A Guide to the Documents from the County Manager's Library, 1889-1994
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
- County Manager's Personal Files
  - References on County Government
    - County Government in Virginia, Frank K. Gibson & Edward S. Overman, UVA, 1961 (Box 34)
    - Contemporary County Government Organization in Arlington County VA, Seminar, Kenneth H. Neubauer, University of Maryland (UMD), 1964 (Box 34)
    - Study Commission of the City/County Form of Government, Preliminary report, 1979 (Box 34)
    - Two county government organization charts, 1936 & undated (Box 34)
    - Organization charts, County Government, 1963 (OVERSIZE) (Box 34)
  - Consumer information
    - Press releases, reports, various subjects, 1940-1950 (Box 34)
    - School Board selection, newsletter, Citizens' Committee for School Improvement, 1946 (Box 34)
    - Handbook, County Government Organization, 1952 (Box 34)
    - You, Arlington, VA & the Nation's Capital, County Board, 1955 (Box 34)
    - Handbook on County Government Organization, 1956 (Box 34)
    - Handbook on County Government Organization, 1964 (Box 34)
    - At Your Service, Annual Reports, 1950, 1965 (Box 34)
    - Reports to the Citizens of Arlington County, VA 1967-1972 (Box 34)
    - Reports to the Citizens of Arlington County, VA 1974-1976, 1979, 1981, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Law Enforcement publications
    - Take-Home Vehicles for High Visibility Patrol, Q & A, The Police Chief, 1973 (Box 35)
    - Criminal Justice in 2000 AD, U of Chicago, 1974 (exerpt) (Box 35)
    - Criminal Activity in Arlington County, Office of Management Systems and Budget, 1975 (Box 35)
    - Criminal Activity in Green Valley, Office of Management Systems and Budget, 1975 (Box 35)
    - Evaluation of the Arlington County Foot-Patrol Program, Office of Management Systems & Budget, 1976 (Box 35)
  - Zoning
    - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (scattered) (Box 35)
    - Mace Properties Zoning Request, Rosslyn, 1945 (Box 35)
    - Rosslyn-Ballston Corridor Studies, Numbers 2 - 7 with correspondence, 1970 (Box 35)
    - Summary of the Arlington County Zoning Ordinance, County Manager (no date) (Box 35)
    - Site Plan Approval Procedure, County Manager, 1970 (Box 35)
    - "C - O" Committee materials, 1970-1971 (scattered) (Box 35)
    - "C - O" Committee materials, 1980 (Box 35)
  - Personnel
    - Regulations for employees, 1930 (?) (Box 35)
    - Position Classification Plan, Public Administration Service, 1947 (Box 35)
    - Salary Plan, Public Administration Service, 1947 (Box 35)
    - Salary Plan, Report & Recommendations, County Manager, 1948 (Box 35)
    - Institutional Inspector, classification, 1950 (Box 35)
    - Personnel Employment Schedule, March 1952 (Box 35)
    - Valuation of Supplemental Retirement Sys, Wyatt Co, 1957 (Box 35)
    - Revised Classification & Pay Plans, Report, J. L. Jacobs & Co, 1961 (Box 35)
    - Revised Classification & Pay Plans, Annex E, Class Specifications, J. L. Jacobs & Company, 1961 (Box 35)
    - Position Classification & Pay Survey Report, James O. Yarger & Associates, 1962 (Box 36)
    - Telephone directories, General Government & Public Schools, 1974-1985 (scattered) (Box 36)
    - Telephone Directories, General Government & Public Schools, 1993, 1994 (Box 36)
    - Organizational charts, 1946-50 (scattered) (Box 36)
  - Commonwealth's Attorney, opinions, related material various subjects (scattered)
    - 1932 (Box 36)
    - 1933 (Box 36)
    - 1934 (Box 36)
    - 1935 (Box 36)
    - 1940 (Box 36)
    - 1944 (Box 36)
    - 1946 (Box 36)
    - 1947 (Box 36)
    - 1948 (Box 36)
    - 1949 (Box 36)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 36)
    - 1952 (Box 36)
    - 1964 (Box 36)
    - 1968 (Box 36)
    - 1975 (Box 36)
  - Departmental Annual Reports (15 Volumes on shelf)
    - 1949 (FY) (Box 36)
    - 1950 (Box 36)
    - 1952 (Box 36)
    - 1953 (Box 36)
    - 1954 (Box 36)
    - 1955 (Box 36)
    - 1956 (Box 36)
    - 1957 (Box 36)
    - 1958 (Box 36)
    - 1959 (Box 36)
    - 1960 (Box 36)
    - 1963 (Box 36)
    - 1965 (Box 36)
    - 1966 (Box 36)
    - 1967 (Box 36)
- Transportation
  - Airports
    - Municipally Owned Airports in Virginia Cities, 1944 (Box 36)
    - Airport Accounts, Municipal Finance Officers Association, 1945 (Box 36)
    - Northern VA Regional Airport Authority Study Committee, 1958 (Box 36)
    - "Air Travel Demand in Washington-Baltimore Region, 1977-1990," 1968 (Box 36)
    - Air Facilities Planning in Metro Washington, 1968 (Box 36)
    - "Washington National & Dulles International Airport Forecasts FY 1970-1981," 1969 (Box 36)
  - Growth Patterns
    - Profile, 1974 (Box 37)
    - Transit Station Impact Analysis, Summary, 1974 (Box 37)
  - Streets and Highways
    - Proposed Street Lighting System Report, Line Material Co. 1936 (Box 37)
    - Highway Lighting Recommendations, Westinghouse (contains non-Arlington photos), 1936 (Box 37)
    - Street & Sidewalk Construction, League of VA Municipalities, 1938 (Box 37)
    - Street Lighting Survey, General Electric, (contains non-Arlington photos), 1943 (Box 37)
    - Highway Improvement Program for Washington Metro Area, Vol 4, Regional Hwy Planning Committee, 1952 (OVERSIZE) (Box 37)
    - Highway Transportation in Washington Metro Area of Virginia, Wilbur Smith & Associates, 1953 (Box 37)
    - Cost of Financing VA Municipal Highways, UVA, 1953 (Box 37)
    - Survey of Alleys, 169 Field Inspection Sheets, 1956, 1957 (Box 37)
    - Dedicated & Public Alleys, Survey Report, 1956 (Box 38)
    - Street Lighting Survey, General Electric, 1959 (Box 38)
    - Cost of Financing VA Municipal Highways for 1959, UVA, 1960 (Box 38)
    - Highway Influence, Northern Virginia Region, Regional Planning & Economic Development Commission, 1962 (Box 38)
    - 1985 Traffic Forecast for Central Potomac River Crossings (I-266), VA and Washington, DC Highway Departments, 1964 (Box 38)
    - "Traffic Needs in Dulles Airport Highway Corridor, 1970-1980," 1964 (Box 38)
    - Street & Storm Sewer Construction Specifications, 1964 (Box 38)
    - A Program of Highway Improvement 1966-1975, Highway Commission of Virginia, 1965 (Box 38)
    - Freeways in National Capital Region, Federal City Council 1966 (Box 38)
    - Virginia's Highways: A Plan for Growth, 1966-1975, VA Highway Commission, 1965 (Box 38)
    - Urban Streets & Highways Beyond 1975, VA Department of Highways, 1967 (Box 38)
    - Highway & Storm Sewer Construction Standards, 1967 (Box 38)
    - The Freeway in the City, Fed Highway Administrator, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Street & Storm Sewer Construction Specs, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Location & Design Study Report, Interstate 595 (Jeff Davis Corridor), n.d. (Box 38)
    - Interstate 595, Environmental Statement, Federal Highway Administration, 1973 (Box 38)
    - Interstate 595, Aurora Highlands Comments, 1973 (Box 38)
    - Virginia's Action Plan for Federally Funded Highway Improvement Projects, VA Department of Highways, 1973 (Box 39)
    - Marcey Road Informational Report, 1974 (Box 39)
    - Public Input to Draft Master Thoroughfare Plan, Summary, 1975 (Box 39)
    - Shirley Highway Operations Study, JHK & Assoc., 1976 (Box 39)
    - Erosion & Sediment Control Handbook, 1977 (Box 39)
    - Jefferson Davis Hwy - Crystal City Traffic Analysis, 1982 (Box 39)
    - Extending Shirley Highway HOV Lanes (final), JHK & Associates, 192 (OVERSIZE) (Box 39)
    - Reconstruction of Jefferson Davis Highway Through Crystal City, Design Manual, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Parking
    - Legality of Parking Meters, League of Virginia Municipalities, 1936 (Box 39)
    - Experience of Municipalities Throughout Country with Parking Meters, League of VA Municipalities, 1938 (Box 39)
    - Off-Street Parking, U.S. Chamber of Commerce, 1949 (Box 39)
    - Automobile Parking Facilities in County, 1950 (Box 39)
    - Parking Program for Clarendon Business Area, 1951 (Box 39)
    - Parking Needs of Office Buildings, (Part 2) 1954 (Box 39)
    - Revised Parking Ordinance (draft), 1959 (Box 39)
    - Clarendon Parking Survey, 1960 (Box 39)
    - Parking Facility Design Study, Court House, 1979 (Box 39)
    - Proposed Ballston Galleria Garage, Feasibility Analysis, Final Report, Wilbur Smith & Assoc., 1982 (Box 39)
  - Traffic Court Inventory Reports
    - 1958 (Box 39)
    - 1959 (Box 40)
    - 1964 (Box 40)
    - 1965 (Box 40)
  - Traffic Safety
    - Traffic Accidents & Statistics, County Safety Committee, 1941 (Box 40)
    - Analysis of National Traffic Safety Contest Report, National Safety Council, 1946 (Box 40)
    - National Pedestrian Protection Contest Report, AAA 1947 (Box 40)
    - Annual Inventory of Traffic Safety Activities, National Safety Council, 1948 (Box 40)
    - Annual Inventory, 1949 (Box 40)
    - Annual Inventory, 1950 (Box 40)
    - Annual Inventory, 1952 (Box 40)
    - Annual Inventory, 1953 (Box 40)
    - Annual Inventory, 1957 (Box 40)
    - AAA Pedestrian Program Appraisal, 1957 (Box 40)
    - AAA Pedestrian Program Appraisal, 1958 (Box 40)
    - Annual Inventory of Traffic Safety Activities, National Safety Council, 1958 (Box 40)
    - Annual Inventory, 1960 (Box 40)
    - Annual Inventory, 1963 (Box 40)
    - Annual Inventory, 1964 (Box 40)
    - Annual Inventory, 1965 (Box 40)
  - Taxicabs and Buses
    - Taxicab Rates for Arlington, Public Utilities Commission, 1961 (Box 40)
    - Taxicab Regulations Study, County Manager, 1962 (Box 40)
    - Arlington Taxicab Industry, Public Utilities Commission, 1965 (Box 40)
    - Shared-Ride Taxi Study (draft), Henry J. Kaufman, 1977 (1) (Box 41)
    - Shared-Ride Taxi Study (draft), Henry J. Kaufman, 1977 (2) (Box 41)
    - Shared-Ride Taxi Study (final) 1977 (Box 41)
    - Paratransit Service for Intra-County Trips, Arlington County Department of Transportation, 1977 (Box 41)
  - Other Studies and Plans
    - 1925 Transportation Survey (District of Columbia), Vols 1 & 2, McClellan & Junkersfield, Inc. (Box 41)
    - Arlington Shopping & Travel Study, U.S. Bureau of Public Roads, 1952 (Box 42)
    - Memorandum of Agreement, Coordinated Transportation Planning, National Capital Region, 1952 (Box 42)
    - Traffic Counts & Allocation of Secondary Highway Funds, VA Department of Highways, 1953 (Box 42)
    - Preliminary Public Buildings Report, Office of Planning, Arlington County, 1959 (Box 42)
    - Arlington County Traffic Operations Study, VA Department of Highways, 1962 (Box 42)
    - Rosslyn Traffic Study, Alan M. Voorhees, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Work Program, Transportation Planning, Washington Metro Area, Alan M. Voorhees, 1964 (Box 42)
    - Review of Rosslyn Traffic Study, Alan M. Voorhees, 1966 (Box 42)
    - Annual Report, N VA Transportation Commission, 1967 (Box 42)
    - Northern VA Topics Study (Traffic) JHK & Assoc., 1972 (OVERSIZE) (Box 42)
    - N VA Transportation Commission, Biennial Report 1972 & 1973 (Box 42)
    - Transportation Study of Aurora Highland-Arlington Ridge Neighborhoods, Arlington Department of Transportation, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Transportation Incentives & Deterrents for County Employees, Arlington Department of Transportation, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Pentagon City Transportation Analysis, R.H. Pratt, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Peak Period Transit Passenger Volume, 1975 Compared to 1978, Department of Public Works, 1979 (Box 43)
    - 1985 Master Transportation Plan (draft), Public Works, Planning (1) (Box 43)
    - 1985 Master Transportation Plan (draft), Public Works, Planning (2) (Box 43)
    - Columbia Pike Land Use & Zoning Study (revised draft), 1986 (Box 43)
- Environmental Affairs
  - Reports
    - Little Pimmit Run Drainage Study - Hayes, Seay, Mattern & Mattern, 1967 (Box 43)
    - Swimming Pool Report, 1969 (Box 43)
    - Census '70: Report No. 3, Population & Housing, 1971 (Box 43)
    - An Analysis of the Open Channel of Doctor's Run, (Preliminary), 1972 (Box 43)
    - "Annual Report - Environmental Quality 1972," 1973 (Box 43)
    - Inventory & Analysis of "M-1" & "M-2" Districts & Proposed Zoning Ordinance Amendments, 1974 (Box 43)
    - Long Range Improvement Program: correspondence, & outline for a report, 1973-1975 (Box 43)
    - Physical Development 1: Pentagon City Tract, 1975 (Box 43)
    - Physical Development 2: The Growth Debate, 1975 (Box 43)
    - Physical Development 3: Clarendon Redevelopment, 1975 (Box 43)
- Economic Development
  - Reports
    - Economic Survey of the Land Uses, 1951 (Box 43)
    - Commercial Development & Zoning, Prelim, 1957 (Box 43)
    - General County Data, 1974-1975 (Box 43)
    - Capital Improvements for Economic Development, 1978 (Box 43)
    - Economic Fact Book, 1978 (Box 44)
    - Preliminary List of Businesses, 1982 (Box 44)
    - Selected Major Businesses, 1982 (Box 44)
    - Court House Plaza Prospectus, 1982 (Box 44)
    - Summary of Development Trends, 1982 (Box 44)
    - Analysis of Demand for Continuing Higher Education, 1983 (Box 44)
    - Profile of New Commercial Development, 1988 (Box 44)
- County Board
  - Minutes, Agendas (by month)
    - January 1932 (Box 44)
    - February 1932 (Box 44)
    - March 1932 (Box 44)
    - April 1932 (Box 44)
    - May 1932 (Box 44)
    - June 1932 (Box 44)
    - July 1932 (Box 44)
    - August 1932 (Box 44)
    - September 1932 (Box 44)
    - October 1932 (Box 44)
    - November 1932 (Box 44)
    - December 1932 (Box 44)
    - January 1933 (Box 44)
    - February 1933 (Box 44)
    - March 1933 (Box 44)
    - April 1933 (Box 45)
    - May 1933 (Box 45)
    - June 1933 (Box 45)
    - July 1933 (Box 45)
    - August 1933 (Box 45)
    - September 1933 (Box 45)
    - October 1933 (Box 45)
    - November 1933 (Box 45)
    - December 1933 (Box 45)
    - January 1934 (Box 45)
    - February 1934 (Box 45)
    - March 1934 (Box 45)
    - May 1934 (Box 45)
    - June 1934 (Box 45)
    - July 1934 (Box 45)
    - August 1934 (Box 45)
    - October 1934 (Box 45)
    - November 1934 (Box 45)
    - January 1935 (Box 45)
    - February 1935 (Box 45)
    - March 1935 (Box 45)
    - April 1935 (Box 45)
    - May 1935 (Box 45)
    - June 1935 (Box 45)
    - July 1935 (Box 45)
    - August 1935 (Box 45)
    - September 1935 (Box 45)
    - October 1935 (Box 45)
    - November 1935 (Box 45)
    - December 1935 (Box 45)
    - January 1936 (Box 45)
    - February 1936 (Box 46)
    - March 1936 (Box 46)
    - April 1936 (Box 46)
    - May 1936 (Box 46)
    - June 1936 (Box 46)
    - July 1936 (Box 46)
    - August 1936 (Box 46)
    - September 1936 (Box 46)
    - October 1936 (Box 46)
    - November 1936 (Box 46)
    - December 1936 (Box 46)
    - January 1937 (Box 46)
    - February 1937 (Box 46)
    - March 1937 (Box 46)
    - April 1937 (Box 46)
    - May 1937 (Box 46)
    - June 1937 (Box 46)
    - July 1937 (Box 46)
    - August 1937 (Box 46)
    - September 1937 (Box 46)
    - October 1937 (Box 46)
    - November 1937 (Box 46)
    - December 1937 (Box 46)
    - January 1938 (Box 46)
    - February 1938 (Box 46)
    - March 1938 (Box 46)
    - April 1938 (Box 46)
    - May 1938 (Box 46)
    - June 1938 (Box 46)
    - July 1938 (Box 46)
    - August 1938 (Box 46)
    - September 1938 (Box 46)
    - October 1938 (Box 46)
    - November 1938 (Box 46)
    - December 1938 (Box 46)
    - January 1939 (Box 46)
    - February 1939 (Box 47)
    - March 1939 (Box 47)
    - April 1939 (Box 47)
    - May 1939 (Box 47)
    - June 1939 (Box 47)
    - July 1939 (Box 47)
    - August 1939 (Box 47)
    - September 1939 (Box 47)
    - October 1939 (Box 47)
    - November 1939 (Box 47)
    - December 1939 (Box 47)
    - January 1940 (Box 47)
    - February 1940 (Box 47)
    - March 1940 (Box 47)
    - April 1940 (Box 47)
    - May 1940 (Box 47)
    - June 1940 (Box 47)
    - July 1940 (Box 47)
    - August 1940 (Box 47)
    - September 1940 (Box 47)
    - October 1940 (Box 47)
    - November 1940 (Box 47)
    - December 1940 (Box 47)
    - January 1941 (Box 47)
    - February 1941 (Box 47)
    - March 1941 (Box 47)
    - April 1941 (Box 47)
    - May 1941 (Box 47)
    - June 1941 (Box 47)
    - July 1941 (Box 47)
    - August 1941 (Box 48)
    - September 1941 (Box 48)
    - October 1941 (Box 48)
    - November 1941 (Box 48)
    - December 1941 (Box 48)
    - January 1942 (Box 48)
    - February 1942 (Box 48)
    - March 1942 (Box 48)
    - April 1942 (Box 48)
    - May 1942 (Box 48)
    - June 1942 (Box 48)
    - July 1942 (Box 48)
    - August 1942 (Box 48)
    - September 1942 (Box 48)
    - October 1942 (Box 48)
    - November 1942 (Box 48)
    - December 1942 (Box 48)
    - January 1943 (Box 48)
    - February 1943 (Box 48)
    - March 1943 (Box 48)
    - April 1943 (Box 48)
    - May 1943 (Box 48)
    - June 1943 (Box 48)
    - July 1943 (Box 48)
    - August 1943 (Box 48)
    - September 1943 (Box 48)
    - October 1943 (Box 48)
    - November 1943 (Box 49)
    - December 1943 (Box 49)
    - January 1944 (Box 49)
    - February 1944 (Box 49)
    - March 1944 (Box 49)
    - April 1944 (Box 49)
    - May 1944 (Box 49)
    - June 1944 (Box 49)
    - July 1944 (Box 49)
    - August 1944 (Box 49)
    - September 1944 (Box 49)
    - October 1944 (Box 49)
    - November 1944 (Box 49)
    - December 1944 (Box 49)
    - January 1945 (Box 49)
    - February 1945 (Box 49)
    - March 1945 (Box 49)
    - April 1945 (Box 49)
    - May 1945 (Box 49)
    - June 1945 (Box 49)
    - July 1945 (Box 49)
    - August 1945 (Box 49)
    - September 1945 (Box 49)
    - October 1945 (Box 49)
    - November 1945 (Box 49)
    - December 1945 (Box 49)
    - January 1946 (Box 49)
    - February 1946 (Box 49)
    - March 1946 (Box 49)
    - April 1946 (Box 50)
    - May 1946 (Box 50)
    - June 1946 (Box 50)
    - July 1946 (Box 50)
    - August 1946 (Box 50)
    - September 1946 (Box 50)
    - October 1946 (Box 50)
    - November 1946 (Box 50)
    - December 1946 (Box 50)
    - March 1947 (Box 50)
    - April 1947 (Box 50)
    - May 1947 (Box 50)
    - June 1947 (Box 50)
    - July 1947 (Box 50)
    - August 1947 (Box 50)
    - September 1947 (Box 50)
    - October 1947 (Box 50)
    - November 1947 (Box 50)
    - December 1947 (Box 50)
    - January 1948 (Box 50)
    - February 1948 (Box 50)
    - March 1948 (Box 50)
    - April 1948 (Box 50)
    - May 1948 (Box 50)
    - June 1948 (Box 50)
    - July 1948 (Box 51)
    - August 1948 (Box 51)
    - September 1948 (Box 51)
    - October 1948 (Box 51)
    - November 1948 (Box 51)
    - December 1948 (Box 51)
    - Action Summaries, 1948 (Box 51)
    - January 1949 (Box 51)
    - February 1949 (Box 51)
    - March 1949 (Box 51)
    - April 1949 (Box 51)
    - May 1949 (Box 51)
    - June 1949 (Box 51)
    - July 1949 (Box 51)
    - August 1949 (Box 51)
    - September 1949 (Box 51)
    - October 1949 (Box 51)
    - November 1949 (Box 51)
    - December 1949 (Box 51)
    - Action Summaries, 1949 (Box 51)
    - Regular Meeting, Junuary 13, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, January 27, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, Feburary 10, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Special Meeting, February 14, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, February 24, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, March 10, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Recessed Meeting, March 15, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, March 24, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, April 7, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, April 21, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Budget Meeting, April 23, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Recessed Meeting, April 30, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, May 5, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Recessed Meeting, May 8, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Zoning Meeting, May 8, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Recessed Zoning Meeting, May 9, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, May 19, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Recessed Meeting, May 24, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, June 2, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Special Meeting, June 14, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, June 16, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, June 30, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Recessed Zoning Meeting, June 30, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, July 14, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, July 28, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Recessed Meeting, July 28, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Special Meeting, August 8, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, August 11, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Recessed Meeting, August 21, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Regular Meeting, August 25, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, September 8, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, September 22, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Rent Control Hearing, October 5, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, October 6, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, October 20, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, October 27, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, November 3, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, November 8, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Semi-Annual Zoning Meeting, November 13, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, November 17, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Zoning Meeting, November 19, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, November 21, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, November 23, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, November 27, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, December 1, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Special Meeting, December 12, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, December 15, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, December 29, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Zoning Meeting, December 29, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Special Meeting, January 2, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, January 12, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, January 15, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, January 21, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, January 26, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, February 9, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, February 19, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, February 23, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, February 25, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, February 28, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, March 3, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, March 8, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, March 14, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, March 22, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, April 5, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Budget Hearing, April 9, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Business Privilege License Hearing, April 17, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, April 19, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting, April 29, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting on Tax Rate, April 30, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, May 3, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting for Zoning, May 13, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Recessed Meeting for Zoning, May 14, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, May 17, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Regular Meeting, May 31, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular and Recessed Meeting, June 2, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, June 14, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, August 9, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Recessed Zoning Meeting, August 9, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, August 23, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Special Meeting, August 25, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Recessed Meeting, August 25, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, September 6, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Recessed Meeting, September 8, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, September 20, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Special Meeting, September 25, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Special Meeting, September 30, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, October 4, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Recessed Meeting, October 9, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Special Meeting, October 17, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, October 18, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Special Meeting, October 28, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, November 1, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting for Zoning, November 12, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, November 15, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Recessed Meeting, November 20, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Recessed Meeting, November 22, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, November 29, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Recessed Meeting, December 9, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Recessed Meeting for Zoning, December 9, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Recessed Meeting for Zoning, December 10, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, December 13, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Regular Meeting, December 27, 1952 (Box 54)
    - County Board Background [filed in 1952 minutes] (Box 54)